tralopia.com 2013-05-07

# Privacy Policy | Tralopia

In compliance with Organic Law 15/1999 from 13th December, about Personal Data Protection, we inform you that the personal information you provide will be stored and processed in files owned by TRALOPIA S.L. in order to attend to your request and provide the due service, and to keep you informed, even via electronic means, on issues related to the company’s activities and its services. 

Be advised that you may exercise at any time, your right of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition of your personal data via email at info@tralopia.com or in writing to Calle Roque No. 22, Postal Code: 38330, Guamasa, Santa Cruz de Tenerife, Spain. 

We appreciate that you trust Tralopia.com to make your hotel reservations. Therefore, we will adequately protect the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information (including your credit card details). 

This privacy policy applies to all of our services whether you've accessed them online or through another platform or device (collectively known as the "Website"). 

Gathering Information 

When you make a reservation at a hotel (or any another type of accommodation), you must complete an online form with your: name, address (home or office), email address (business or private), telephone number (mobile, home or office), the credit card details (credit card type, number, CVC, expiry date, cardholder name, etc.) and, where possible, booking preferences for the room, be it smoking or non-smoking, etc. This information is required to process, carry out and close your booking (including sending a booking confirmation email). 

Disclosure of Personal Information 

To provide our services we require the following information: 

Reservation requests: 

In order to finish and close your booking and with the exception of disclosures required by law, criminal investigations, subpoenas or court orders, we will only disclose your name, your contact information and the your credit card details to the hotel at which the reservation is made. However, keep in mind that at some point we may use other vendors that provide services and operate on our behalf. These distributors have access to (part of) your personal information to be able to offer you their services, but are subject to a confidentiality agreement by which they cannot use, share or disclose the information for any other purpose. 

Surveys: 

When making a reservation, you agree to receive an email invitation to complete the review form which will be sent to you upon termination of your stay at the hotel, and can be completed anonymously. By filling this form, you agree that the completed form will be loaded in the respective hotel information page of our website and other social platforms owned or controlled, managed or offered (in whole or in part) by us or our partners with the sole purpose of informing (potential) customers of your opinion of the service (level) and quality of the hotel. We reserve the right to modify, reject or remove reviews. The feedback form is a survey and does not include offers, invitations or inducements of any kind. 

Newsletters and other information: 

If you wish to receive our newsletter, offers or other information (relating to our products and services or those of our affiliates or partners), we offer a subscription option. If you no longer wish to receive the newsletter and offers, you can click on the "unsubscribe". 

Visitors Registration, system access, use of "cookies" and web beacons: 

In order to (improve) our service and products, we use "cookies" (temporary and permanent) and authorized "cookies" by third-parties, web beacons and/or other technologies to collect non-personal identifiable information (such as IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP) and (for those who access our service via a mobile device) device unique identifier, operating system and latitude/longitude (the "Non-Personal Identifiable Information") and to track web browsing behaviour, make specific or "custom" offers and advertisements and monitor and record the visits and the use of our website(s) . 

To understand how users use our Website, conduct market research and improve the quality of service, we collect, store, process and use (anonymously) some data, like the total number of transactions, web sites visited, reference/exit pages, platform type, information on date/time and data such as the number and location of the (mouse) clicks on a particular page, mouse movements, scrolling activity and the searches for words and texts that you write when you use our website (the “Data"). 

In addition, we also collect and use your Non-Personal Identifiable Information for behavioural approach campaigns, possible fraud, misuse and criminal investigations. 

Please note that sometimes we use external service providers for market research to improve the quality of service ("Service Providers"). We also use Service Providers to track visitor’s detailed activity or for specific pages. These service providers collect, use, monitor and report on data and statistics collected and analyse your online activities on our website. Information on the use of our website (including your non-personal identifiable information) is transmitted to and stored on the servers of the Service Providers. In addition, these Service Providers may also transfer the information collected to third parties where requested by law or where such third parties process the information on behalf of the Service Provider. 

By visiting our web site, we do not share personal information about customers with our Service Providers. These service providers will not collect any personal identifiable information (Personal identifiable information "PII"). Personal Identifiable Information does not include your IP address, type of browser, Internet Service Provider, the unique identifier of the device, the operating system or the latitude/longitude. We are permitted to share and display your data and personal information if required by law, governmental authorities (or any statutory of legal status), legal processes, criminal investigations, or subpoenas. 

About "cookies" and web beacons: "Cookies" are text files, temporary or permanent, which are stored on the hard drive of your computer. They are used for authenticating, session tracking (maintenance status) and to conserve specific information about users of our site, such as site preferences or the contents of their electronic shopping carts. The "cookie" files can also be stored on your computer by other companies of our trusted advertising companies that share the same objectives set forth in this paragraph. The information which these “cookies” collect is completely anonymous. If you prefer, you can erase all "cookies" from the hard drive of your computer, by searching for files containing "cookie" and deleting them and for future reference, you can edit your browser settings to block (future) cookies. However, keep in mind that if you block these, you will not be able to use all the features on our website. For more information on (the use and reduction of) cookies, visit: allaboutcookies.org 

The web beacon is a number of software codes that represent a graphic image on a website or an email. There may be a visible graphic image associated with the beacons, and usually the image is designed in harmony with the background of the website or email. The web beacons can be used for various purposes, including traffic reports, count of solely visitors, review and report on advertising, and personalization. Web beacons used by Tralopia.com collect only anonymous data. 

Protecting your privacy online 

In accordance with European legislation on data protection, the strict security measures taken at Tralopia.com are designed to prevent misuse and unauthorized access to personal data. 

Tralopia.com uses trustworthy advertising and marketing systems, and analytics companies committed to consumer awareness and the responsible management of companies and data. 

Take into account that if you unsubscribe from a network, that does not mean you're not going to receive or be subject to advertising and online market analysis. This does not imply that the network, from which you have unsubscribed, is not allowed to send advertisements tailored to your web preferences and usage patterns. 

Protection of your credit card information 

In order to protect and safeguard your personal data, we have implemented the appropriate business systems and procedures. For example, the information of your credit card is transmitted via a secure server protocol, which encrypts all your personal information and your credit card data. The encryption method used is "Secure Socket Layer" (SSL). The SSL certificate has been issued by Thawte: www.thawte.com 

In addition, we have implemented and used security procedures, technical and physical restrictions to avoid access to and use of personal information. Only authorized personnel can access the personal information to carry out their work in relation to our services. 

Our server and network is protected by firewalls against unauthorized access and we have intrusion detection systems that monitor and detect unauthorized access (or attempted) or misuse of our servers. 

Control of your data 

You will be able to review your personal data at any time. You can request your personal data by sending an email to: [  customer.service@tralopia.com](mailto:%20customer.service@tralopia.com)

The email subject should state "Request for personal data." 

If your personal data is incorrect, you can request it be modified. You may also ask Tralopia.com to remove your data from its database by sending an email to the address mentioned above. 

When does Tralopia.com send emails? 

You will receive a confirmation email once you have finished the booking process. We recommend that you print the confirmation email and present it upon arrival at your hotel. Before your arrival we will send you an email with information about your destination and other useful offers and relevant information (including external offers that you've agreed to receive). Also, after your stay at the hotel, we will send you another email inviting you to complete a review form. This report is loaded onto the hotel's information page on our website and other social platforms owned or controlled, managed or offered (in whole or in part) by us or our partners with the sole purpose of informing (future ) customers of your opinion of the service (level) and quality of the hotel. If you've signed up for the "voluntary subscription" you will receive our newsletter and other information of interest. 

Contact 

Tralopia S.L is the party responsible for processing your personal information. This is a private limited company incorporated under the laws in Spain and with headquarters in Guamasa, Calle El Roque number 22, Postal code: 38330, Santa Cruz de Tenerife, Spain. 

If you have any suggestions or comments about this privacy policy, please send an email to: [  customer.service@tralopia.com](mailto:%20customer.service@tralopia.com)

We reserve the right to modify at our convenience, how we collect, transmit and process personal information and other data, as we deem necessary. This privacy statement may be corrected at any time in order to reflect recent changes.
